<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming with R</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Programming with R</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019. AbdulMajedRaja - All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Find out Bulk Email ID Reputations Risk using R</title>
      <link>/find-out-bulk-email-id-reputations-risk-using-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/find-out-bulk-email-id-reputations-risk-using-r/</guid>
      <description>If you are working in Info Sec / Cyber Security, One of the things that might be part of your day job is to filter email to remove spams / phishing emails. While this could be done at several levels and ways, monitoring the email id (like abc@xyz.com) and validating its reputation to see if it seems risky / suspicious or authentic and then allowing them to reach the user inbox - is one of the solid ways (while it’s also error-prone with False Positives).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Blogs</title>
      <link>/r-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r-blogs/</guid>
      <description> R-Bloggers  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to embed Excel-like Spreadsheet Table in RMarkdown</title>
      <link>/how-to-embed-excel-like-spreadsheet-table-in-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-embed-excel-like-spreadsheet-table-in-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>If there’s a component that’s least interactive in an RMarkdown rendered document or a Shiny app - that’d be the Table that’s displayed. Yes, datatable does a good job of improving the Table Apperance and custom formatting like Conditional Formatting, it doesn’t give a Google Spreadsheet or Microsoft Excel flavor. This post is to let you know how you can embed that excel-like spreadsheet Table in your Rmarkdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to do negation-proof sentiment analysis in R</title>
      <link>/how-to-do-negation-proof-sentiment-analysis-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-do-negation-proof-sentiment-analysis-in-r/</guid>
      <description>Sentiment Analysis is one of those things in Machine learning which is still getting improvement with the rise of Deep Learning based NLP solutions. There are many things like Sarcasm, Negations and similar items make Sentiment Analysis a rather tough nut to crack.
Deep learning as much as it’s effective, it’s also computationally expensive and if you are ready to trade off between Cost (expense) and Accuracy, then you this is the solution for building a negation-proof Sentiment Analysis solution (in R).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Thank you visiting us. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got a feedback / suggestion or you&amp;rsquo;d like to write for us?
Contact us @ contact@programmingwithr.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Programming with R is an attempt to share the knowledge of R Programming to the larger world. Typically, It includes :
 How-To Tutorials R Tips &amp;amp; Tricks New Package Details  and similar content to promote the richness of R and its versatility.
Thanks for reading!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>